rvt.com 2011-12-28

# RVT Privacy Agreement

Last Updated: June 29 2010

**Natco Trading Corporation, DBA RV Trader** has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us. If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint).

RV Trader is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of the RV Trader Classifieds.   
  
---|---|---  
  
This policy will let you know: 

  1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you
  2. What cookies are and how they are used
  3. Log Files
  4. Email-A-Friend
  5. Newsletters
  6. Links to Other Sites
  7. Payment Process
  8. Who is collecting your information
  9. Public Display of Personally Identifiable Information
  10. Testimonials
  11. With whom your information may be shared
  12. Service Providers
  13. Legal Disclaimer
  14. Choice / Opt-out
  15. Communications From Our Site
  16. How you can access, update or delete your information
  17. The kind of security precautions that are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information
  18. How Natco Trading protects children's privacy
  19. What else you should know about your online privacy
  20. Changes in this Privacy Statement

* * *

### What personally identifiable information is collected from you

The RV Trader Classifieds collects information in several ways from different parts of our web site from the buyers, users and dealers. 

Personal information is gathered when you register as a user or a dealer on our site. During registration, we ask for personally identifiable information such as, name and email address, street address, city, state/province, zip/postal code, country, telephone number, company name, vehicle information, and the URL of your web site, although only fields that are marked with an asterisk (*) on the registration field are required. This information is used solely to assist you in navigating the system by automatically filling in certain forms (such as the ad posting form) with your information so that you don't have to continually re-enter it. Once you register you are no longer anonymous to RV Trader - you have a username and are able to take full advantage of the many offerings of the RV Trader Classifieds. 

In addition to registration we ask you for personal information at other times, including (but not limited to) when you place ads or take advantage of the other features of the RV Trader Classifieds such as Auto Notify, Dealer Inventory, and Contact us. We use the information submitted only to provide the service you have requested and for no other purpose. If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence. Every page within the RV Trader Classifieds includes a link to this Privacy Policy. 

If you choose not to register or provide personal information, you can still use most of the RV Trader Classifieds, but you will not be able to access areas or use features that require registration. 

Back to Top

* * *

### What cookies are and how they are used

As part of offering and providing customizable and personalized services, the RV Trader Classifieds uses [cookies](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie) to store and track information about you. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Several features of the RV Trader Classifieds require that you accept cookies in order to work properly. 

Generally, we use cookies for the following purposes and they are not tied to personally identifiable information: 

(1) To identify and label all "new" ads since your last visit to the site. 

(2) Optionally to permanently save your password on your computer so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. 

(3) To enable you to "checklist" ads that you want to mark for future retrieval and viewing. 

By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject all cookies you will be unable to use those services of the RV Trader Classifieds that require registration in order to participate. These services include the identification of new ads that have been posted since your last visit, auto-fill in of the logon form, and the Checklist feature. You can still use most of the features of the RV Trader Classifieds even if you do not accept cookies. 

Advertising networks that serve ads onto the RV Trader Classifieds may also use their own cookies. We have no access to or control over these cookies. 

We use a third-party tracking service that uses cookies to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate. 

Back to Top

* * *

### Log Files

The RV Trader Classifieds may also collect IP addresses via the use of log files for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site, to report aggregate information to our advertisers, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do not link this automatically collected data to personally identifiable information. 

Back to Top

* * *

### Email-A-Friend

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. RV Trader does not store this information. 

Back to Top

* * *

### Newsletters

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe. Please see the "Choice and Opt-out" section below. 

Back to Top

* * *

### Links to Other Sites

This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by RV Trader. Please be aware that we, RV Trader are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by these Web sites as denoted by the URLs described at the beginning of this statement. 

Back to Top

* * *

### Payment Process

When you pay for your orders on our site you will be taken to a third party site to complete the transaction. Their privacy policy governs the collection and use of the information submitted. We encourage you to view their privacy policy. 

Back to Top

* * *

### Who is collecting your information

When you are asked for personal information on the RV Trader Classifieds, you are sharing that information with the RV Trader Classifieds alone, unless it is specifically stated otherwise. When you visit our order/payment pages, you will be on a trusted third party site to complete your transaction. Please see their privacy statement for more information on what they collect from you and how they use this information. 

Back to Top

* * *

### Public Display of Personally Identifiable Information

Some functions on our site will, by their very nature, result in your personal information being revealed to other users of the RV Trader Classifieds. For example, when you enter personal information on the ad posting form, this information will generally be included in your ad, unless specifically stated otherwise. Please be aware that information that you submit in your classified ad can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in your ad listings or on these forums. 

Back to Top

* * *

### Testimonials

We use testimonials on our Web Sites(s). We receive permission to post the testimonials in advance of their posting. If you would like your testimonial removed at any time, please contact us at [tradersupport@rvt.com](mailto:tradersupport@rvt.com). 

Back to Top

* * *

### With whom your information may be shared

RV Trader will not share any of your personally identifiable information with third parties except our service providers without your prior and explicit consent and only as described in this privacy statement. 

Back to Top

* * *

### Service Providers

We use a third party email service provider on our site. We will share information with this service provider as necessary for the third party to provide this service. This third party is prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose including their own marketing purposes. 

Back to Top

* * *

### Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site. 

Back to Top

* * *

### Choice / Opt-out

We provide you the opportunity to 'opt-in' to receive our periodic newsletter. You can do so at various areas of the site by providing your email address or by checking the box to receive our newsletter. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at [tradersupport@rvt.com](mailto:tradersupport@rvt.com). 

Back to Top

* * *

### Communications From Our Site

You will receive a confirmation email upon placing an ad and notification emails just prior to the expiry of a placed ad. Emails are sent weekly to notify you of new ad postings according to your specified criteria when using the "Auto Notify" feature of a User Account. We will also send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. Generally, you may not opt-out of these service related communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account by emailing [tradersupport@rvt.com](mailto:tradersupport@rvt.com) or calling 800-677-4484. You may opt-out of these communications. Please see "Choice / Opt-out" above. 

Back to Top

* * *

### How you can access, update or delete your information

We will provide you with the means to ensure that your personal information is correct and current. You may edit or delete your user profile at any time by clicking on the "My Profile" link or graphic provided by the system once you are logged in. Once you have logged onto the system during a given session, wherever you go on the RV Trader Classifieds, your information will stay with you until or unless you click on the "Logout" link, which is accessible at the top of every page. If you are a previously registered user and you have lost or forgotten your password, you may obtain it by email by using our "Forgot Password" feature. Click the button on any login page to request that your password be emailed to you. We cannot provide your password by any other means. Your RV Trader Classifieds account can be deleted by emailing [tradersupport@rvt.com](mailto:tradersupport@rvt.com) or calling 800-677-4484, but doing so will result in not being able to access any of the features of the program that require user registration. If you have any questions regarding your account, please contact us at [tradersupport@rvt.com](mailto:tradersupport@rvt.com). 

Back to Top

* * *

### The kind of security precautions that are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information

Other than the administrator of the RV Trader Classifieds or other authorized personnel of the RV Trader, you are the only person who has access to your personal information. Your user registration is password-protected to prevent unauthorized access. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. RV Trader will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. As an extra security precaution, you may want to logoff once you have completed a session in the RV Trader Classifieds. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or Internet cafe. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, RV Trader cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. 

Back to Top

* * *

### How RV Trader protects children's privacy

RV Trader is a general audience web site and is not intended for anyone under the age of 13. We do not collect age identifying information on our site, however, if we find out that someone under the age of 13 has submitted information to our site, we will delete this information immediately. 

Back to Top

* * *

### What else you should know about your online privacy

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example in ads that you post or through email - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online. 

Back to Top

* * *

### Changes in this Privacy Statement

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. 

Back to Top

Natco Trading Corporation  
1102-1329 Ellis St.  
Kelowna, British Columbia  
Canada V1Y 9X5  

Back to Top
